

MY CONTACT

shivammmishra7@gmail.com



+91 9870031209



in Shivam Mishra



https://shivam-m-7.vercel.app/



https://github.com/shivam-m-7



Surat, Gujarat

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Masai School

Full-stack Web Development course May-2022 to March-2023

Gujarat Technological University Bachelor's in I.T Engineering June-2018 to May-2021

Gujarat Technological University Diploma in I.T Engineering June-2015 to May-2018

INTERNSHIP

Om System Design

Asp.Net Intern

Contributed in a product, school management system using TechStack C#, javascript, SQL, AJAX.

06/2018-01/2019

Surat, Guiarat

TECH SKILL

- ReactJS
- Java C# AWS Flask
- NodeJS
- SQL
- MongoDB

- Vue JS
- ExpressJS • Git
- Microsoft Azure
- JavaScript DSA
- Python

SOFT SKILL

- Quick Learner
- Communication
- Time Management
- TeamWork

INTRESTS

- **Outdoor Sports**
- Yoga
- Travel

Shivam Mishra **FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

ABOUT ME

An inspired MERN stack developer, always curious about new problems and learning new things in order to deliver out of the box solutions with complete ownership. Hands on experience in solving close to 500 DSA problems and developing five MERN based projects

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Engross Infotech

Surat, Gujarat

Serving on an International E-Commerce Project Lakeshore using technology like KnockoutJS, Java, Endeca, Bootstrap, Jquery, XM, and SQL.

06/2023-current

Full Stack Developer

Om System Design

Surat, Gujarat

- In addition to contributing to a number of projects implementing ReactJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, SQL, C#, SQL, Javascript, Bootstrap, and Git technologies, I was in the role of designing, building, and maintaining a web application.
- projects on AWS and Azure cloud platforms and hosted them.

05/2021-06/2023

PROJECTS

Shopping Ganga

Source Code

- This MERN stack e-commerce site is a powerful Backend Heavy and comprehensive online store, designed and built individually, with intuitive design and user-friendly interface. Webapp provides admin panel with administration privileges like product listing, user profile management, delivery data.
- Features -export Data in PDF, sending mails, PayPal, cart management, order summary, filter, search.
- Tech Stack ReactJs, NodeJS, Mongo Atlas ,PayPal API, Material UI.

Practo.com Clone

- Practo is the world's leading healthcare platform that connects millions of patients with hundreds of thousands of healthcare providers around the world and helps people make better healthcare decisions.
- Developed along with a team of 4 members in one week.
- Created a dynamic profile page for doctors using redux and appointment list for users.
- Tech Stack React, Node, MongoAtlas, Chakra-UI, Redux, ExpressJS, BootStrap, Cyclic, Middleware.

<u>RavenEye</u>

Source Code

- This is a video calling application where users can call other user and will also have the capability to mute their mic and audio.
- Features -real time chat functionality. It's also a modern PWA so users can install it on their devices like other native apps. Unlimited duration calls, Chat Notifications, Chat in real-time.
- Tech Stack PWA, ReactJS, JavaScript, SocketIO, WebRTC, Realtime.